[Music]
I told you to stay your ass is down on
the ground earlier the officer could be
seen chasing boys and cursing as he
forced them to the
ground can I see that barrel roll
again oh my God church has gotten it
wrong a few times on science and I think
that uh you we probably are better off
leaving science to the scientist
okay no I know here's the thing he's
totally right okay he just has no idea
why right I don't think he does okay no
let me take a quick poll okay Round of
Applause how many people would go to an
all black pool
party I hav Hillary Clinton should do
all of her events at black pool party
the nightly show on Comedy Central like
us on Facebook too just don't poke me I
do not like being poked you can Candy
Crush me